https://www.uvirco.com/online-privacy-policy/

ONLINE PRIVACY POLICYBy accessing or using the web site of UViRCO Technologies (Pty) Ltd (“UViRCO”), you agree to the terms of UViRCO’s Online Privacy Policy, as outlined below. If you do not agree to these terms, please do not access or use this site. UViRCO reserves the right to change the Online Privacy Policy from time to time at its sole discretion. Your use of this site will be subject to the most current version of the Online Privacy Policy at the time of such use.This Privacy Policy covers UViRCO’s processing of personally identifiable information that UViRCO collects when you are on their site, and when you use UViRCO’s services. This policy also covers UViRCO’s processing of any personally identifiable information that UViRCO’s business partners share with it.This policy does not apply to companies that UViRCO does not own or control, or to people that UViRCO does not employ or manage.UViRCO will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone.UViRCO will only send personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people when:•	We have your consent to share the information;•	We need to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested;•	We need to send the information to companies who work on behalf of UViRCO to provide a product or service to you (these companies do not have any right to use the personally identifiable information we provide to them beyond what is necessary to assist us);•	We respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process; or•	We find that your actions on our web sites violate any of our usage guidelines for specific products or services.USE OF COOKIESA cookie is small amount of data that is transferred to your browser by a web server and can only be read by the server that gave it to you. It functions as an identification tool, keeping track of logons, purchases, and preferences. It cannot be executed as code or deliver viruses.Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it (for some web pages that require an authorization, cookies are not optional. Users choosing not to accept cookies will probably not be able to access those pages).UViRCO’s use of cookies will not identify you personally unless you have otherwise freely provided UViRCO with personal information.If you have questions or suggestions regarding UViRCO’s online privacy policy, please send an email to info@uvirco.comPRODucTS
CoroCAM® 6HD
CoroCAM® 7
CoroCAM® 8
CoroCAM® 8 UAV
CoroCAM® UVS 1
Intergrators & Custom ProductsTrainingCoroBASE® SoftwareHandheld CamerasUAV CamerasABOUT USWho we are & What we doTimelineCertifications & PAIADisclaimerOnline Privacy PolicyStandard Conditions of SalesAPPLICATIONSCoroCAM®
Applications TECHNOLOGYCoroCAM® TechnologyInspectionsCONTACTContact UsContact a DistributorBecome a Distributorinfo@uvirco.com+27 (12) 349 3760Unit B003, The Woods, 41 De Havilland Crescent, Persequor Technopark, Pretoria, 0020© COPYRIGHT UViRCO TECHNOLOGIES (PTY) LTD 2020. ALL RIGHTS RESERVED.WEBSITE DESIGN BY BLUE WEB TECHNOLOGIES
closemap-markerchevron-downbars
